Guide to the Henry Knox Sherrill Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence, 1776-1986; Series I
  - Family Correspondence
    - 2. Correspondence of family members other than HKS
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Paradise - Pusey (Box 35, Folder 668)
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Quarterman - Rusack (Box 35, Folder 669)
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Schofield - Snyder (Box 35, Folder 670)
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Taft - Washburn (Box 35, Folder 671)
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Weeks - Young (Box 35, Folder 672)
      - BHS -- Letters received after death of HKS: Christian names only, and unidentified (Box 35, Folder 673)
      - Henry W. Sherrill (2nd) (incl. letters after death of HKS re: death of Rosamond Fisher), 1926-1986, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Franklin Goldthwaite Sherrill (2nd), 1935,1978 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - General Correspondence
    - Prominent Correspondents
      - Acheson, Dean, 1949-1971 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Ahuja, Elias, 1933,1937, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Allin, John Maury (Mrs.), 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Angell, James Rowland, 1929-1967 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Atwood, Julius W., 1928-1933, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Austin, Warren R. (U.S. rep. to U.N.), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Babcock, Samuel G., 1923-1936, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Baillie, John (Mrs.), 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Barnes, C. Rankin, 1950, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Barnes, Roswell P., 1958-1970 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Barton, Arthur W., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Bell, Bernard Iddings, 1949, 1950, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Bell, George K. A. Henrietta, 1954-1963 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Bentley, John, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Billings, Sherrard, 1923-1930, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Blair, Edwin Foster, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Blake, Eugene Carson, 1958, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Bowie, Walter Russell, 1928-1968 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Brent, Charles Henry, 1923-1928 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Brewster, Kingman, 1968-1977 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Briggs, Mrs. Ellis, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Brown, Charles R., 1924, 1930, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - Bruning, Heinrich, 1941, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Bush, George, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Bush, Prescott S., 1949-1972 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Carpenter, Edward, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Carpenter, Walter S., Jr., and the 3rd, 1949-1971 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - Carrington, Philip, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Cavert, Samuel McCrea, 1946-1970 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - Coburn, John B., 1964-1976, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - Coffin, Dorothy (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - Coffin, Henry Sloane, 1930-1949, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr., 1962, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Coggan, Donald, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Conant, James B., 1936-1949 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Cooke, Mrs. Montague, Jr., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Crocker, Jack, 1955-1965 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Cushing, Richard, 1946, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Dallas, John T., 1928-1954 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Dandridge, E. P., 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Davis, Champion McD., 1950-1970 (Box 4, Folder 86)
      - Day, Gardiner M., 1933, 1962, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Dickey, Charles, 1946-1974 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Dillistone, Frederick W., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Donegan, Horace B., 1946-1970 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Drown, Edward and Paulina, 1917, 1923-1932, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Dulles, John Foster, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Dun, Angus, 1926-1970 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - du Vivier, Gabrielle, 1919, 1930, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 94)
      - Dykman, Jackson A., 1958, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - Episcopal Church Foundation, 1967-1974 (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Faxon, Nathaniel, 1947-1970 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Ferris, Theodore P., 1952-1972, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Fisher, Geoffrey, 1945-1956 (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - Fisher, Geoffrey, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Fisher, Geoffrey, 1962-1969 (Box 4, Folder 102)
      - Fisher, Geoffrey, 1970-1972 (1977) (Box 4, Folder 103)
      - Fisher, Rosamond, 1958-1979, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 104)
      - Foot, Dingle, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Forman, Margaret, 1963-1972 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Forrester, Jay, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 197)
      - Fosbroke, Hughell, 1923-1951 (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Freund, Paul A., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Fry, Franklin C., 1957,1966 (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - Garbett, Cyril (and Elsie), 1949, 1950, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - Gardner, George Peabody, 1949-1970 (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - Garland, Thomas, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 113)
      - Germanos, Bp., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - Good Samaritan Foundation (see also: Carpenter, W. S.), 1945-1975 (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - Gordon, George A., 1924-1929 (Box 5, Folder 116)
      - Gray, Francis C., 1946-1966 (Box 5, Folder 117)
      - Grenfell, Wilfred and Anne, 1920-1937 (Box 5, Folder 118)
      - Grenfell, Wilfred and Anne, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 119)
      - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1955-1961 (Box 5, Folder 120)
      - Hand, Learned, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 121)
      - Harriman, Averell, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 122)
      - Herd, John Victor, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 123)
      - Hines, John E., 1949-1967, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - Hobson, Henry W., 1928-1977 (Box 5, Folder 125)
      - Holden, Reuben A., 1946-1962 (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - Kennedy, Harry, 1948, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - Kennedy, John F., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - Kinsolving, Arthur B., 1930-1960 (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1947, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Lawrence, W. Appleton and Hannah, 1923-1968 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - Lawrence, W. Appleton and Hannah (Box 5, Folder 132)
      - Lawrence, Frederick C., 1930-1977, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - Lawrence, William, 1914-1941 (Box 5, Folder 134)
      - Lawrence, William, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 135)
      - Lewis, Wilmarth, 1946-1959 (Box 5, Folder 136)
      - Lichtenberger, Arthur, 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 137)
      - Lovett, Sidney, 1942-1958, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 138)
      - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1932, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 139)
      - Luce, Henry R., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 140)
      - Mann, Alexander, 1914, 1923-1943 (Box 5, Folder 141)
      - Mann, John G., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 142)
      - Marshall, George Catlett, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 143)
      - Means, Howard, 1930-1965 (Box 5, Folder 144)
      - Moors, Ethel L. Paine, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 145)
      - Mott, John R., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 145)
      - Mowll, H. W. K. and Dorothy, 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 146)
      - Murray, John G., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 147)
      - Nash, Norman, 1928, 1932, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 148)
      - Neill, Stephen C., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - Newbiggin, Lesslie, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - Niebuhr, H. Richard, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - 0' Connell, William, 1936-1943 (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - Oldham, Ashton, 1950, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 152)
      - Oxnam, G. Bromley, 1946-1960 (Box 6, Folder 153)
      - Paine, Robert Treat, 1917, 1926-1936 (Box 6, Folder 154)
      - Peabody, Endicott, 1930-1943 (Box 6, Folder 155)
      - Peabody, Francis, 1928-1 936 (Box 6, Folder 156)
      - Peabody, Malcolm, 1923-1959, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      - Peabody, Marian, 1964, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 158)
      - Pepper, George Wharton, 1928, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 159)
      - Perry, James DeWolf, 1919-1945, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 160)
      - Phelps, William Lyon, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 161)
      - Pope, Liston, 1957-1962 (Box 6, Folder 162)
      - Pusey, Nathan and Anne, 1962-1977 (Box 6, Folder 163)
      - Quin, Clinton S., 1949, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 164)
      - Ramsey, Michael, 1949-1960 (Box 6, Folder 165)
      - Reinhardt, John W., 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 166)
      - Ridgway, Caleb, Jr., 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 167)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 168)
      - Rose, Lawrence, 1952, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 169)
      - Ross, Roy G., 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 170)
      - Rousmaniere, Edmund, 1920-1924, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 171)
      - Rowe, Peter T., 1927-1941 (Box 6, Folder 172)
      - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1943-1958 (Box 6, Folder 173)
      - Sayre, Francis B., 1947-1972 (Box 6, Folder 174)
      - Scarlett, Willam and Leah, 1936, 1958-1971 (Box 6, Folder 175)
      - Seymour, Charles, 1946-1961, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 176)
      - Shepherd, Massey H., Jr., 1944-1971 (Box 6, Folder 177)
      - Shipman, Herbert, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 178)
      - Shriver, Robert Sargent, 3r., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 179)
      - Slattery, Charles Lewis, 1921-1928 (Box 6, Folder 180)
      - Smith, Eugene L., l958, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 181)
      - Sperry, Willard, 1928-l953 (Box 6, Folder 182)
      - Stafford, Philip H., 1932, 1947-1963,n.d. (Box 6, Folder 183)
      - Stires, Ernest, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 184)
      - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1946, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 185)
      - Stopford, Robert and Kathleen, 1964-1977 (Box 6, Folder 186)
      - Strong, Philip, 1950-1963 (Box 6, Folder 187)
      - Sturges, Philemon, 1932, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 188)
      - Sullivan, Edward T., 1926-1936 (Box 6, Folder 189)
      - Suter, John, 1936, 1949, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 190)
      - Taft, Charles, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 191)
      - Taylor, Charles, 1945-1977 (Box 6, Folder 192)
      - Temple, William and Frances, 1936-1953 (Box 6, Folder 193)
      - Thayer, Ethel, 1946, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 194)
      - Truman, Harry S., 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 195)
      - Tucker, Beverly D., 1928, 1954-1968 (Box 6, Folder 196)
      - Tucker, Henry St. George, 1939-1945, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - Van Dusen, Henry Pitney, 1946, 1962, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 198)
      - van Etten, Edwin, 1919-1946, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 199)
      - Visser 't Hooft, W. A., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 200)
      - Warren, Matthew M., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 201)
      - Washburn, Bradford, 1946-1967, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 202)
      - Washburn, Henry B., 1914, 1921-1961 (Box 7, Folder 203)
      - Weeks, Sinclair, 1958, 1961, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 204)
      - Weeks, Edward, 1961-1976 (Box 7, Folder 205)
      - Weigle, Luther A., 1946, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 206)
      - White, Paul Dudley, 1940, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 207)
      - Wilmer, Richard, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 208)
      - Winslow, Charles, 1932, 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 209)
      - Wright, William, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 210)
      - Yashiro, Michael, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - Chronological sequence of correspondence received at notable events
      - 1923 decision: A - W (Box 7, Folder 212-230)
      - 1928 decision: A - Sn (Box 8, Folder 231-251)
      - 1928 decision: So - Y, fragment (Box 9, Folder 252-256)
      - 1929 Yale honorary D.D.: A - Y (Box 9, Folder 257-260)
      - 1930: Bishop of Massachusetts: A - Fu (Box 9, Folder 261-273)
      - 1930: Bishop of Massachusetts: Ga - Y (Box 10, Folder 274-300)
      - 1932, 1933: Deaths of mother and brother: A - P (Box 11, Folder 301-312)
      - 1932, 1933: Deaths of mother and brother: R-W, Christian name only (Box 11a, Folder 313-317)
      - 1943 William Lawrence book: A - W (Box 12, Folder 318-323)
      - 1945 Trip to Europe for General Commission on Army and Navy Chaplains: A - W (Box 12, Folder 324-326)
      - 1945 15th Anniversary of consecration: A - W (Box 12, Folder 327-328)
      - 1947 Presiding Bishop: A - F (Box 12, Folder 329-341)
      - 1947 Presiding Bishop: I - Z, Christian names (Box 13, Folder 342-356)
      - 1949 Operation: A - H (Box 13, Folder 357-360)
      - 1949 Operation: J - Y (Box 14, Folder 361-366)
      - 1955 25th Anniversary of consecration: A - W (Box 14, Folder 367-375)
      - 1958 Television show: A - W, Christian names (Box 14, Folder 376-377)
      - 1958 Retirement: A - Z (Box 14, Folder 378-384)
      - Bound volume of letters from fellow bishops and friends (Box 14, Folder 385)
      - 1962 Publication of Among Friends: A - Z (Box 15, Folder 386-404)
      - 1968 Operation (Box 15, Folder 404A)
      - 1970 80th birthday: A - Y (Box 15, Folder 405-414)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence
      - A - Z, unidentified (Box 16, Folder 415-443)
- Sermons, Writings, 1914-1972, n.d.; Series II
  - 1914
    - Thesis on the Atonement, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - 1922-1928
    - "Judaizing the Argument" ( The Churchman ), 1922 Apr 10 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Sermon, 1922 Feb 18 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Sermon, 1922 Apr 11 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "The Right Reverend Alexander Mann" ( The Church News ), 1923 Feb (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "The Living Christ and Daily Living" ( Record of Christian Work ), 1925 Sep (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "If I Were in the Seminary Again!" ( The Intercollegian ), 1925 Dec (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "Discipline and Discipleship" (Southern Churchman ), 1926 Aug 7 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "Christ and the Multitude" ( Christian Leader ), 1927 Mar 26 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "The Power of Friendship" ( Cathedral Quarterly ), 1927 Oct (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Address to Men's Supper, 1927 Dec (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - "The Appeal of Christmas" ( American Mutual Magazine ), 1928 Dec (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - 1930-1938
    - "Religion and Social Service" ( Connecticut Churchman ), 1930 Apr (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Prayer, 1930 Dec 14 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Announcement re: Office hours ( Church Militant ), 1931 Jan (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Finances and the Diocese" ( Church Militant ), 1931 Feb (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The Christian Ministry", 1931 Mar 27 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - "The Greatest Profession in the World" ( Church Militant ), 1931 Apr (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Easter message, 1931 Apr 4 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Convention address ( Church Militant ), 1931 May (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The Life of the Spirit" ( Cathedral Quarterly ), 1931 Oct (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Prayer before Armistice Day, 1931 Nov 8 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Today's Call to the Church" ( Christian Century ), 1932 Jan (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Sermon at annual Conference at Diocese of Pittsburgh, 1932 Jan 26 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Palm Sunday "Sermonette" ( Living Church ), 1932 Mar 19 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Our Diocese and Our Church" ( Church Militant ), 1932 Mar (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Convention address ( Church Militant ), 1932 Apr 12 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Baccalaureate sermon, General Theological Seminary, 1932 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Radio broadcast (WNAC, Boston), 1932 Sep 11 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Mind, Heart, and Soul" ( Church Militant ), 1932 Oct (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Our Responsibility in Recruiting the Ministry" ( Church Militant ), 1932 Nov (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Christmas message "The Living God" (Lent meditation guide) 1933 Lent, 1932 Dec (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Address before Greater Boston Federation of Churches, 1933 Mar 24 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Anniversary sermon ( Trinity Life ), 1933 Nov 19 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The New Year" ( Church Militant ), 1934 Jan (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The Living Christ and the Future of Our Civilization" ( Church Militant ), 1934 Apr (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Commencement address, Northfield Seminary, 1934 Jun 10 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - "William Greenough Thayer" ( Church Militant ), 1934 Dec (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Christmas greeting ( Church Militant ), 1934 Dec (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Address at 80th anniversary of Temple Israel, 1934 Dec 7 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Appeal for mission funds, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Message ( Church Militant ), 1935 Mar (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Sermon: 100th anniversary of the birth of Phillips Brooks, 1935 Dec 8 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Article re: church and conscientious objectors, 1935 Dec 28 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Fourth Lenten broadcast (WEEI), 1936 Mar 20 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Seventh Lenten broadcast (WEEI), 1936 Apr 10 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Convention of our Diocese Met April 29" ( Church Militant ), 1936 May (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Commencement address, Trinity College, 1936 Jun 15 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Address to Harvard Alumni Association, 1936 Jun 18 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The Difficulty We Confront" ( The Witness ), 1936 Jun 18 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Address at 250th anniversary of King's Chapel Boston, 1936 Nov 18 (Box 36, Folder 678)
    - Christmas message, 1936 Dec (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "Religion and Education", 1937 Apr 22 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Address: memorial service for Rev. Carroll Perry, 1937 Oct 31 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Review of Murder in the Cathedral by T.S. Eliot, 1938 Feb 2 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Sermon, 1938 Feb 16 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - "The Word of Life" ( Zions Herald ), 1938 Mar 2 (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - 1940-1945
    - Tenth Annual Address to 155th Diocesan Convention ( Church Militant ), 1940 Apr 9 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Address at 75th anniversary of St. Mark's School, 1940 May 25 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Message, ca. 1940 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "In Memory of Dean Sturges" (Church Militant, 1941 Feb), 1941 Jan 19 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Address on the life of Phillips Brooks, 1941 Apr 17 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "Full Time" ( Church Militant ), 1941 Apr (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "Sanity and Strength" ( Church Militant ), 1941 Nov (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Address in memory of Dr. Wilfred Grenfell, 1941 Feb 28 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Sermon at consecration of Rev. Oliver J. Hart, 1942 Oct 16 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "Sacrificial Giving" ( Church Militant ), 1942 Nov (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "We Are the Church" ( Church Militant ), 1942 Dec (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Sermon: 20th anniversary of Bishop Mann's consecration, 1943 Jan 26 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "War and the Arts of Peace" ( Church Militant ), 1943 Jan (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Address at Y.M.C.A. dinner, 1943 Jun 15 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Sermon: consecration of the very Rev. Angus Dun, D.D., 1944 Apr 19 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "The Invasion and Religion" ( Church Militant ), 1944 Jun (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Address: 100th anniversary of the Church of the Advent, Boston, 1944 Dec 3 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Radio broadcast, 1945 Jan (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - 5 articles re: trip to Europe to confer with chaplains, 1945 Aug 11-15 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Sermon at 15th anniversary of HKS's consecration, 1945 Oct 14 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - "Hope or Despair" ( The Witness ), 1945 Dec 13 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - "We Care for Them" ( Forth ), 1945 Dec (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Writings re: Europe tour, ca. 1945 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - 1946
    - Sermon at 35th anniversary of consecration of Bp. Perry, 1946 Jan 6 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Address at Women's Republican Club, 1946 May 20 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - Sermon at consecration of R. Emrich, 1946 Jun 11 (Box 36, Folder 679)
    - War Memorial Service, Hatch Memorial Shell, 1946 Sep 1 (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - "Atomic Bomb vs. Christmas Peace", ca. 1946 (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - Untitled address, ca. 1946 (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - 1947
    - Address at installation of HKS as Presiding Bishop, 1947 Jan 14 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Broadcast message to Radio Free Europe, 1947 Jan (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - "A Call to All Churchmen" ( Forth ), 1947 Jan (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Address: "The Present World Crisis and Christian Education", 1947 Mar 28 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Radio broadcast: "Our Times and Eternity" (WEEI, Boston), 1947 Apr 13 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Address re: Rev. Hughell Fosbroke, 1947 May 7 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Thanksgiving radio address, 1947 Nov (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Biographical sketch of Hughell Fosbroke (revised 1954), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 439)
  - 1948
    - Address to Protestant Council, 1948 Jan 31 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Radio address, 1948 Feb 29 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Brief address, 1948 Apr 1 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Address to General Conference of the Methodist Church, 1948 May 2 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Lambeth Inaugural Service, 1948 Jul 4 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Address to St. Augustine's College,England, 1948 Jul (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Message: "Human Values in a World of Science", 1948 Oct 21 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Christmas message ( Forth ), 1948 Dec (Box 17, Folder 440)
  - 1949
    - Message: "Our Expanding Church", 1949 Mar 3 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Message, 1949 May (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Message, 1949 Sep 9 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Address: opening service of 56th General Convention, 1949 Sep 26 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - "A Call to Consecration" ( The Witness ), 1949 Oct 13 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Message, 1949 Oct 14 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Address re: 56th General Convention, 1949 Oct 16 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Christmas message, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - 1950
    - Article re: Diocesan Investment Trust, 1950 Feb 10 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Radio address, 1950 Mar 12 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Review of Dr. Dawley's book, 1950 Mar 20 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Review of Dr. Allport's book, 1950 Apr 10 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Easter message ( Forth ), 1950 Apr (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Message, 1950 May 23 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Prayer, 1950 Sep (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Message (from address to General Convention), 1950 Oct 18 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Message re: National Council of Churches, 1950 Nov 13 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Closing message to the Constituting Convention of the National Council of Churches, 1950 Dec 1 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Christmas message, 1950 Dec 14 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Christmas message, 1950 Dec 22 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Call to Prayer, 1950 Dec 31 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Christmas message ( Forth ), 1950 Dec (Box 17, Folder 442)
  - 1951
    - Message, 1951 Jan 31 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message re: Religious Education Week, 1951 Feb 26 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Messages for dedication of St. Paul's Church, Cleveland Heights, OH, 1951 Feb 26 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message to the Society for the Propagation of the Gospel, 1951 Mar 14 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Address to the YWCA, St. Louis, 1951 Apr 4 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Address, 1951 May 27 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Independence Day message, 1951 Jul 1 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message, 1951 Sep 17 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Statement on morality ( Young America World Parade ), 1951 Sep 24-28 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message re: giving to the Church, 1951 Sep 25 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Memorial address for Russell E. Dill, 1951 Oct 1 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Television broadcast, 1951 Oct 7 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Sermon, 1951 Oct 19 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message, 1951 Oct 26 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message re: morality, 1951 Nov 20 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Message re: NCCC, 1951 Nov 27 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - "Liberty at a Price" ( Zions Herald ), 1951 Nov 28 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Address to Nat'l Association of Manufacturers, 1951 Dec 7 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - New Year's greeting to NCCC, 1951 Dec 14 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Christmas message ( Journal American ), 1951 Dec 17 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Christmas message, 1951 Dec 22 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Christmas message, 1951 Dec (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - "The Meaning of Christmas" ( True Story ), 1951 (Box 17, Folder 443)
  - 1952 Jan-Jun
    - Message to NCCC, 1952 Jan 2 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Address to the Annual Assembly of the Division of Foreign Missions, 1952 Jan 4 (Box 18, Folder 444)